asianetdataline.com 2014-06-25

# Asianet Broadband

|    
---  
  
Testimonials

Mr.Cleetez B. Fernandez.

Quote : " We are the resident of Canada and of course we did not find any difference in your service between the services we do receive in Canada. Congratulations to ASIANET Team members. Keep it on."  

Trivandrum prepaid renewal  
Contact:9446094445,  9142761681 9400758939,9400758929  
Cochin Prepaid Renewal  
Contact:9961456240, 6467240, 2339766, and 2342075   
Kollam Prepaid Renewal 9847300724  
Kottayam Prepaid Renewal  
98474 73559 , 0481 2580313  
|  Privacy Policy  
---  
|  asianetdataline.com is sensitive to privacy issues on the Internet and is committed to safeguarding the privacy of user online.  
---  
asianetdataline.com collects personally identifiable data such as names, addresses and e-mail addresses that are voluntarily submitted by a user when he/she wishes to become a registered user of the services provided.  
Personal information collected is used in the following manner. One of the reasons to collect information from users registering on asianetdataline.com is to customise the services at asianetdataline.com. The more information the user volunteers the better the experience on asianetdataline.com  
asianetdataline.com would also use cookies to customise the services provided to the user. These are small amounts of data that are sent to the user's browser from the web server and stored in the user's hard disk. You are required to accept cookies wherever you are prompted to login. These are basically Zip codes that categorise the user based on interests and behaviour.  
Personal information is used to deliver targeted advertisements to the user according to the specifications of the advertiser. This does not imply that the advertiser or any third party has an access to user's personal information. They will only receive aggregated user statistics (e.g. 60 % of our users are professionals. Only asianetdataline.com has access to Users' accounts.  
asianetdataline.com will notify users prior to sharing the information collected with a partner of asianetdataline.com or a sponsor of an event. You could choose not to allow that transfer by not using the service or by not participating in that particular event.   
Users should be aware that when they voluntarily disclose personal information on chat areas, that information can be collected and used by others and may result in unsolicited messages from other parties.  
asianetdataline.com shall not reveal any personal information that users provide to us, to any third party without the users' permission, unless, asianetdataline.com has a reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating the Terms of Use, or may be causing injury to, or interfering with the rights or property of itself, other users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. asianetdataline.com may disclose or access account information when it believes in good faith that the law requires it and for administrative and other purposes that we deem necessary to maintain, service and improve our products and services.   
asianetdataline.com is not responsible for the privacy practices employed by advertisers or sites to which links are provided by asianetdataline.com  
Information provided by all Users needs to be true, accurate, current and complete as required by the registration form and promptly updated to keep it true, accurate, current and complete. The privacy policy covers exchanges of personally identifiable information within sites of asianetdataline.com.
